{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"9.0.2","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":990,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":11,"width":1024,"height":627,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"si1998","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5315q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5327","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5315q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5338","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5340","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Social Determinants of Health: Pre-Test ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5398","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5360","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"According to the CDC, all of the following are social determinants of health EXCEPT:  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5375","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5379","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Safe homes and neighborhoods  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5375_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Safe homes and neighborhoods \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5386","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5390","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Stable employment  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5386_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Stable employment\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5561","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5565","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Quality education  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5561_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Quality education\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5576","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5580","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Access to foods that promote healthy eating patterns  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5576_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Access to foods that promote healthy eating patterns\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5591","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5595","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Genes and biology  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5591_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Genes and biology\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si5402","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide5315q0","for":"Slide5315q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5416","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide5315q0","for":"Slide5315q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5430","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5315q0","for":"Slide5315q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5599","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5315q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5612","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5315q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5625","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"The correct response is E. Per the CDC, a, b, c and d are social determinants of health. E is a health determinant but not a social determinant of health.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5315q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5315","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1998","si5327","si5338","si5340","si5360","si5379","si5390","si5565","si5580","si5595","si5402","si5416","si5430","si5612"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5315"},"question":{"interactionId":"5347","quizId":380,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"According to the CDC, all of the following are social determinants of health EXCEPT: \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si5894","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5891q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5905","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5907","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Social Determinants of Health: Pre-Test ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5756","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_13","roles":{}},{"id":"si5684","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_2","title":"According to the Centers for Disease Control (CDC), which of the following MOST predicts a person’s longevity and health? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5695","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_3","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5699","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_4","title":"Person’s Genetic Code  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5695_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Person’s Genetic Code\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5706","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_5","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5710","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_6","title":"Person’s Zip Code  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5706_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Person’s Zip Code\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si5717","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_7","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5721","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_8","title":"Person’s Physical Activity  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5717_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Person’s Physical Activity\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5728","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_9","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5732","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_10","title":"Person’s Diet  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5728_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Person’s Diet\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5782","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_1","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide5891q1","for":"Slide5891q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_2","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide5891q1","for":"Slide5891q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5812","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_3","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5891q1","for":"Slide5891q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5831","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_1","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5891q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5862","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5891q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5881","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_3","title":"The correct response is B. Per the CDC, a person’s zip code predicts a person’s longevity and health more than his or her genetic code, physical activity or diet.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5891q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5891","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1998","si5894","si5905","si5907","si5684","si5699","si5710","si5721","si5732","si5782","si5796","si5812","si5862"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5891"},"question":{"interactionId":"5664","quizId":380,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"According to the Centers for Disease Control (CDC), which of the following MOST predicts a person’s longevity and health?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si6152","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6149q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6163","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6165","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Social Determinants of Health: Pre-Test ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6014","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_24","roles":{}},{"id":"si5953","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_15","title":"People who work in environments that offer them little control over the circumstances of their work have higher rates of:   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5964","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_16","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5968","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_17","title":"Mental Illness  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5964_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_11","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Mental Illness\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5975","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_18","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5979","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_19","title":"Heart disease  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5975_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_12","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Heart disease\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5986","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_20","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5990","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_21","title":"Sickness absence  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5986_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_13","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Sickness absence\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5997","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_22","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6001","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_23","title":"All of the above  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5997_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_14","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si6040","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide6149q2","for":"Slide6149q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6054","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_5","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide6149q2","for":"Slide6149q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6070","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_6","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6149q2","for":"Slide6149q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6089","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_4","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6149q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_5","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6149q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6139","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_6","title":"The correct response is D. People with little control over circumstances of their work have higher rates of mental illness, heart disease and sickness absence.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6149q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6149","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1998","si6152","si6163","si6165","si5953","si5968","si5979","si5990","si6001","si6040","si6054","si6070","si6120"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6149"},"question":{"interactionId":"5933","quizId":380,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"People who work in environments that offer them little control over the circumstances of their work have higher rates of: \r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si6410","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6407q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6421","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6423","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Social Determinants of Health: Pre-Test ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6272","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_35","roles":{}},{"id":"si6211","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_26","title":"All of these data obtained from a first patient visit information survey and an initial history are indicators for social determinants of health that may negatively impact health outcomes EXCEPT: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6222","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_27","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6226","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_28","title":"Age: 18 years  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6222_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_15","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Age: 18 years\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6233","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_29","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6237","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_30","title":"Gender: Female  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6233_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_16","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Gender: Female\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6244","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_31","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6248","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_32","title":"Race/Ethnicity: Hispanic  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6244_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_17","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Race/Ethnicity: Hispanic\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6255","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_33","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6259","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_34","title":"Language(s) Spoken: Spanish  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6255_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_18","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Language(s) Spoken: Spanish\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si6434","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6438","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Education: Recent High school graduate  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6434_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Education: Recent High school graduate \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6449","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6453","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Zip Code:  10456 (Morrisania in the Bronx)  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6449_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Zip Code:  10456 (Morrisania in the Bronx)\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_7","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide6407q3","for":"Slide6407q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6312","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_8","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide6407q3","for":"Slide6407q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6328","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6407q3","for":"Slide6407q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6347","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_7","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6407q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6378","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_8","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6407q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6397","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":"The correct response is D. All but D may negatively impact a person’s health outcomes.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6407q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6407","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1998","si6410","si6421","si6423","si6211","si6226","si6237","si6248","si6259","si6438","si6453","si6298","si6312","si6328","si6378"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6407"},"question":{"interactionId":"6191","quizId":380,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"All of these data obtained from a first patient visit information survey and an initial history are indicators for social determinants of health that may negatively impact health outcomes EXCEPT:\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si6713","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6710q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6724","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6726","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Social Determinants of Health: Pre-Test ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6575","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_48","roles":{}},{"id":"si6503","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_37","title":"You are caring for a 24-year-old Caucasian, pregnant female who immigrated to NYC from Russia. She may experience negative health outcomes based upon all of these EXCEPT:   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6514","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_38","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6518","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_39","title":"Race ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6514_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"19","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Race\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6525","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_40","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6529","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_41","title":"Gender ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6525_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"21","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Gender\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6536","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_42","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6540","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_43","title":"National Origin ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6536_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"23","roles":{"answer":{"title":"National Origin\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6547","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_44","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6551","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_45","title":"Pregnancy ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6547_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"25","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Pregnancy\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6558","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_46","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6562","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_47","title":"Employed as an interpreter ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6558_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"27","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Employed as an interpreter\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si6601","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_10","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide6710q4","for":"Slide6710q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6615","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_11","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide6710q4","for":"Slide6710q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6631","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_12","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6710q4","for":"Slide6710q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6650","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_10","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6710q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6681","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_11","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6710q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6700","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_12","title":"The correct response is E. A, B, C and D may negatively impact this patient’s health outcomes.  Employment as an interpreter will not negatively impact her health.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6710q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6710","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1998","si6713","si6724","si6726","si6503","si6518","si6529","si6540","si6551","si6562","si6601","si6615","si6631","si6681"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6710"},"question":{"interactionId":"6483","quizId":380,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"You are caring for a 24-year-old Caucasian, pregnant female who immigrated to NYC from Russia. She may experience negative health outcomes based upon all of these EXCEPT: \r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si7001","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6998q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7012","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si7014","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Social Determinants of Health: Pre-Test ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6863","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_63","roles":{}},{"id":"si6780","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_50","title":"Adverse Childhood Experiences have been associated with all of the following in adulthood? EXCEPT:  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6791","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_51","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6795","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_52","title":"Substance use disorders ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6791_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_28","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Substance use disorders\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6802","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_53","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6806","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_54","title":"Delayed childbearing  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6802_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_29","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Delayed childbearing\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6813","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_55","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6817","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_56","title":"Poor work performance  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6813_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_30","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Poor work performance\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6824","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_57","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6828","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_58","title":"Depression  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6824_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_31","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Depression\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6835","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_59","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6839","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_60","title":"End stage renal disease   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6835_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"32","roles":{"answer":{"title":"End stage renal disease \r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si6846","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_61","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6850","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_62","title":"Ischemic heart disease  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6846_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"34","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ischemic heart disease\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6889","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_13","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide6998q5","for":"Slide6998q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6903","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_14","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide6998q5","for":"Slide6998q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6919","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_15","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6998q5","for":"Slide6998q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6938","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_13","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6998q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6969","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_14","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6998q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6988","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_15","title":"The correct response is E. Per the ACE study, all of the above but end stage renal disease were found to be related to ACEs.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6998q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6998","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1998","si7001","si7012","si7014","si6780","si6795","si6806","si6817","si6828","si6839","si6850","si6889","si6903","si6919","si6969"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6998"},"question":{"interactionId":"6760","quizId":380,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Adverse Childhood Experiences have been associated with all of the following in adulthood? EXCEPT: \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si7547","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7544q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7558","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si7560","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Social Determinants of Health: Pre-Test ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7409","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_89","roles":{}},{"id":"si7348","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_80","title":"Which of the following screening tools are helpful to include in your clinical practice related to Social Determinants of Health (SDOH)? Please select all that apply. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7359","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_81","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7363","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_82","title":"SCARED Assessment Tool  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7359_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_41","roles":{"answer":{"title":"SCARED Assessment Tool\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7370","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_83","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7374","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_84","title":"Connor’s assessment scale  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7370_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_42","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Connor’s assessment scale\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7381","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_85","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7385","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_86","title":"RESILIENCE Questionnaire  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7381_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_43","roles":{"answer":{"title":"RESILIENCE Questionnaire\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si7392","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_87","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7396","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_88","title":"Health Problems Toolkit  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7392_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_44","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Health Problems Toolkit\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_19","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide7544q6","for":"Slide7544q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7449","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_20","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide7544q6","for":"Slide7544q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7465","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_21","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide7544q6","for":"Slide7544q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7484","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_19","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7544q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7515","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_20","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7544q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7534","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_21","title":"The correct response is C. The Resilience questionnaire is a SDOH assessment tool. The SCARED tool is for assessment of anxiety in school age children. The Connor’s tool is for assessment of ADHD.  D is not a real toolkit.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7544q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7544","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1998","si7547","si7558","si7560","si7348","si7363","si7374","si7385","si7396","si7435","si7449","si7465","si7515"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7544"},"question":{"interactionId":"7328","quizId":380,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Which of the following screening tools are helpful to include in your clinical practice related to Social Determinants of Health (SDOH)? Please select all that apply.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si7820","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7817q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7831","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si7833","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Social Determinants of Health: Pre-Test ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7682","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_102","roles":{}},{"id":"si7610","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_91","title":"Upstream interventions that address root causes of health disparities include all of the following EXCEPT: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7621","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_92","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7625","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_93","title":"Address the context of your patients’ lives.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7621_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"19_45","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Address the context of your patients’ lives. \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7632","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_94","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7636","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_95","title":"Link patients and their families to community resources. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7632_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"21_46","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Link patients and their families to community resources.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7643","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_96","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7647","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_97","title":"Utilize community healthcare workers in the care of your patients and their families.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7643_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"23_47","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Utilize community healthcare workers in the care of your patients and their families.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7654","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_98","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7658","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_99","title":"Advocate for economic and social policies that improve living and working conditions for all persons  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7654_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"25_48","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Advocate for economic and social policies that improve living and working conditions for all persons\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7665","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_100","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7669","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_101","title":"Attendance in a cardiac rehabilitation program post cardiac intervention for treatment of a congenital cardiac defect ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7665_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"27_49","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Attendance in a cardiac rehabilitation program post cardiac intervention for treatment of a congenital cardiac defect\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si7708","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_22","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide7817q7","for":"Slide7817q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7722","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_23","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide7817q7","for":"Slide7817q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_24","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide7817q7","for":"Slide7817q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7757","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_22","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7817q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7788","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_23","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7817q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7807","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_24","title":"The correct response is E. This is a medical factor and all others are recommended interventions related to social determinants of health to improve outcomes for patients   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7817q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7817","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1998","si7820","si7831","si7833","si7610","si7625","si7636","si7647","si7658","si7669","si7708","si7722","si7738","si7788"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7817"},"question":{"interactionId":"7590","quizId":380,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Upstream interventions that address root causes of health disparities include all of the following EXCEPT:\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si8093","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8090q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8104","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si8106","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Social Determinants of Health: Pre-Test ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7955","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_115","roles":{}},{"id":"si7883","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_104","title":"Which of the following social and/or economic policy increases health equity? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7894","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_105","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7898","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_106","title":"Zoning laws that encourage neighborhood fast food outlets ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7894_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"19_50","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Zoning laws that encourage neighborhood fast food outlets\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7905","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7909","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_108","title":"Construction of quality moderate and high income housing in integrated mixed income neighborhoods.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7905_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"21_51","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Construction of quality moderate and high income housing in integrated mixed income neighborhoods.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7916","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_109","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7920","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_110","title":"Reduction in funding and infrastructure for public transportation.n ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7916_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"23_52","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Reduction in funding and infrastructure for public transportation.n\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7927","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_111","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7931","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_112","title":"Adequate enforcement of housing regulations.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7927_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"25_53","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Adequate enforcement of housing regulations. \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si7981","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_25","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide8090q8","for":"Slide8090q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7995","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_26","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide8090q8","for":"Slide8090q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8011","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_27","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8090q8","for":"Slide8090q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8030","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_25","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8090q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8061","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_26","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8090q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8080","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_27","title":"The correct response is D. D represents a social and economic policy that would improve social determinants of health. All other choices would worsen social determinants of health.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8090q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8090","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1998","si8093","si8104","si8106","si7883","si7898","si7909","si7920","si7931","si7981","si7995","si8011","si8061"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8090"},"question":{"interactionId":"7863","quizId":380,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Which of the following social and/or economic policy increases health equity?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si8366","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8363q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8377","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si8379","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Social Determinants of Health: Pre-Test ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8228","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_128","roles":{}},{"id":"si8156","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_117","title":"Which of the following have been found to reduce Adverse Childhood Experiences (ACEs)? Please select all that apply. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8167","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_118","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8171","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_119","title":"Nurse home visits in the prenatal period and first two years of life. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8171","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8363q9"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si8167_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Nurse home visits in the prenatal period and first two years of life.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8178","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_120","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8182","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_121","title":"Parenting training classes. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8182","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8363q9"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si8178_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Parenting training classes.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_122","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8193","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_123","title":"Intimate partner violence prevention.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8193","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8363q9"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si8189_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Intimate partner violence prevention. \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8200","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_124","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8204","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_125","title":"Incarceration of illicit drug users. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8204","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8363q9"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si8200_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Incarceration of illicit drug users.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8211","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_126","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8215","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_127","title":"Preschool enrollment. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8215","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8363q9"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si8211_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Preschool enrollment.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si8254","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_28","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide8363q9","for":"Slide8363q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8268","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_29","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide8363q9","for":"Slide8363q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8284","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_30","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8363q9","for":"Slide8363q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8303","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_28","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8363q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8334","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_29","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8363q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8353","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_30","title":"The correct response is A,B,C, & E. They have all been found to reduce ACEs. Incarceration of a relative is an ACE.    Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8363q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8363","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1998","si8366","si8377","si8379","si8156","si8171","si8182","si8193","si8204","si8215","si8254","si8268","si8284","si8334"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8363"},"question":{"interactionId":"8136","quizId":380,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Which of the following have been found to reduce Adverse Childhood Experiences (ACEs)? Please select all that apply.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A","B","C","E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si5456","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_129","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_129","title":"Click “Continue” to exit. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5478","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5486","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5494","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5502","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5510","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5518","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5467","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5474","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5482","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Maximum Score: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5490","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5498","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5506","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5514","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Attempts: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5522","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5526","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5540","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5446","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5446"}}},{"id":"Pool424","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":424,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"SDOH Pre-Test","class":"project","title":"SDOH Pre-Test","children":["Slide5315","Slide5891","Slide6149","Slide6407","Slide6710","Slide6998","Slide7544","Slide7817","Slide8090","Slide8363","Slide5446"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":380,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide5315q0","Slide5891q1","Slide6149q2","Slide6407q3","Slide6710q4","Slide6998q5","Slide7544q6","Slide7817q7","Slide8090q8","Slide8363q9"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":100,"passScore":90}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":false,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide5315","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide5891","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide6149","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide6407","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide6710","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide6998","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide7544","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide7817","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide8090","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide8363","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide5446","title":"Slide 11"}]}